{
  "categories": [
    {
      "title": "2025 Book Club Hits",
      "clues": [
        {
          "value": 100,
          "question": "In \"God of the Woods\", what year does “Bear” go missing?",
          "answer": "1961"
        },
        {
          "value": 200,
          "question": "Charlie and Eve move to a home on the side of a mountain nicknamed this in \"We Used to Live Here\".",
          "answer": "Stray Dog Summit"
        },
        {
          "value": 300,
          "question": "In \"The Frozen River\", whenever Martha enters Dr. Coleman’s shop, she is hoping not to see this on the counter.",
          "answer": "A silver fox pelt"
        },
        {
          "value": 400,
          "question": "In \"Stillhouse Lake\", Gwen does daily internet research into what internet trolls are saying about her family. What does she refer to this research as?",
          "answer": "Sicko Patrol"
        },
        {
          "value": 500,
          "question": "In \"The Women\" by Kristin Hannah, Frankie goes to recover and get sober after hitting rock bottom at a ranch in this state.",
          "answer": "Montana"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "title": "Relatives and Relationships",
      "clues": [
        {
          "value": 100,
          "question": "In \"Bury Our Bones in the Midnight Soil\", Jocelyn is to Charlotte who?",
          "answer": "Her childhood best friend and first love"
        },
        {
          "value": 200,
          "question": "In \"The Seven Year Slip\", Rhonda is to Clementine who?",
          "answer": "Her boss"
        },
        {
          "value": 300,
          "question": "In \"Funny Story\", Jason is to Holly who?",
          "answer": "Her husband"
        },
        {
          "value": 400,
          "question": "In \"God of the Woods\", Tracy is to Barbara who?",
          "answer": "Her summer camp bunkmate"
        },
        {
          "value": 500,
          "question": "In \"We Are Legion\", Andrea is to Alaina who?",
          "answer": "Her sister"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "title": "Book to Screen Adaptations",
      "clues": [
        {
          "value": 100,
          "question": "This director and star in the film \"It Ends With Us\" was engaged in a lawsuit with costar Blake Lively.",
          "answer": "Justin Baldoni"
        },
        {
          "value": 200,
          "question": "In the second installment of \"The Twilight Saga: New Moon\", the famous line “Where the hell have you BEEN, Loca?” is spoken by this actor.",
          "answer": "Taylor Lautner"
        },
        {
          "value": 300,
          "question": "In what film does a character with lavender hair exclaim, “That is Mahogany!!”?",
          "answer": "The Hunger Games"
        },
        {
          "value": 400,
          "question": "Sam Claflin plays Finnick Odair in \"The Hunger Games\" and this character in the Amazon Prime series \"Daisy Jones & The Six\".",
          "answer": "Billy Dunne"
        },
        {
          "value": 500,
          "question": "The HBO Max series \"Game of Thrones\" is based on this book series by George R. R. Martin.",
          "answer": "A Song of Ice and Fire"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "title": "Modern Best Sellers",
      "clues": [
        {
          "value": 100,
          "question": "This novel features a struggling author who ghostwrites for a famous novelist and discovers sinister secrets about their employer.",
          "answer": "Verity"
        },
        {
          "value": 200,
          "question": "This book, the first in a series, follows a huntress through a magical realm to atone for a crime she committed at the beginning of the story.",
          "answer": "A Court of Thorns and Roses"
        },
        {
          "value": 300,
          "question": "In this Kristin Hannah novel, the main character moves to America’s “Last Frontier” with their abusive father and co-dependent mother.",
          "answer": "The Great Alone"
        },
        {
          "value": 400,
          "question": "This finale novel in a multi-book fantasy series ends with a battle that determines the fate of the world.",
          "answer": "Kingdom of Ash"
        },
        {
          "value": 500,
          "question": "In this 2023 release, the protagonist is forced to join a war college where they face deadly challenges, beasts, and combat.",
          "answer": "Fourth Wing"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "title": "Wait… What’s Their Name?",
      "clues": [
        {
          "value": 100,
          "question": "These men were accused of raping Rebecca Foster.",
          "answer": "Joseph North and Joshua Burgess"
        },
        {
          "value": 200,
          "question": "Matteo’s human lover is named who?",
          "answer": "Alessandro"
        },
        {
          "value": 300,
          "question": "Gwen purchases a vehicle from this man who works at the gun range.",
          "answer": "Javier “Javi” Esparza"
        },
        {
          "value": 400,
          "question": "Frankie’s older brother, who is killed in action, is named who?",
          "answer": "Finley McGrath"
        },
        {
          "value": 500,
          "question": "Grace discovers the disappearance of this local woman.",
          "answer": "Bri Becker"
        }
      ]
    }
  ]
}
